扩写是指将一篇较短的文本进行扩写的工作
Expanding is the task of taking a shorter piece of text
如一套指示或一个主题列表
such as a set of instructions or a list of topics
并让大语言模型生成一个较长的文本
and having the large language model generate a longer piece of text
例如一封电子邮件或一篇关于某些主题的文章
such as an email or an essay about some topic
这方面有一些很好的用途
There are some great uses of this
例如，如果你使用一个大语言模型作为头脑风暴的伙伴
such as if you use a large language model as a brainstorming partner
但是，我也想承认，有一些
But I just also want to acknowledge that there's
有问题的使用案例
some problematic use cases of this
例如，如果有人用它来产生大量的垃圾邮件
such as if someone were to use it to generate a large amount of spam
因此，当你使用大语言模型的这些能力时
So when you use these capabilities of a large language model
请以负责任的方式和帮助人们的方式来使用它
please use it only in a responsible way and in a way that helps people
在这个视频中，我们将通过一个例子来说明
In this video, we'll go through an example of how you can use
如何使用语言模型，生成一个基于某些信息的个性化电子邮件
a language model to generate a personalized email based on some information
这封邮件自称是来自一个AI机器人
The email is kind of self-proclaimed to be from an AI bot
正如恩达提到的，这一点非常重要
which as Andrew mentioned, is very important
我们还将使用另一个
We're also going to use another one of
该模型的另一个输入参数，叫做temperature（温度）
the model's input parameters called temperature
这允许你改变模型的探索和多样性的程度
and this allows you to vary the degree of
这允许你改变模型响应的探索和多样性
exploration and variety in the model's responses
因此，让我们开始吧
So let's get into it
在我们开始之前
So before we get started
我们要做一些常规的设置
we're going to do the usual setup
所以要设置OpenAI Python软件包
So set up the OpenAI Python package
然后定义我们的辅助函数，get_completion
and then also define our helper function, get_completion
现在我们要为客户的评论写一个自定义的电子邮件回复
Now we're going to write a custom email response to a customer review
所以给定一个客户评论和情绪
So given a customer review and the sentiment
我们将生成一个自定义的回复
we're going to generate a custom response
现在我们要使用语言模型来生成
Now we're going to use the language model to generate
根据客户的评论，给客户发送一封定制的电子邮件
a custom email to a customer based on a customer review
和评论的情绪
and the sentiment of the review
所以我们已经提取了情绪
So we've already extracted the sentiment
使用我们在推理视频中看到的那种提示
using the kind of prompts that we saw in the inferring video
然后这就是客户对搅拌机的评论
and then this is the customer review for a blender
现在我们要根据情感来定制回复
Now we're going to customize the reply based on the sentiment
所以这里的指令是
So here the instruction is
你是一个客户服务的AI助理
you are a customer service AI assistant
你的任务是给一个有价值的客户发送电子邮件回复
Your task is to send an email reply to a valued customer
给出客户的电子邮件，以三个`符号分割
Given the customer email delimited by three backticks
产生一个回复，以感谢客户的评论
generate a reply to thank the customer for their review
如果情绪是积极的或中性的
If the sentiment is positive or neutral
感谢他们的评论
thank them for their review
如果情绪是负面的
If the sentiment is negative
道歉，并建议他们可以联系客户服务部
apologize and suggest that they can reach out to customer service
确保使用评论中的具体细节
Make sure to use specific details from the review
用简明和专业的语气来写
write in a concise and professional tone
并以AI客户代理的身份在邮件中签名
and sign the email as AI customer agent
当你使用一个语言模型
When you're using a language model
来生成你要展示给用户的文本
to generate text that you're going to show to a user
有这样的透明度是非常重要的
it's very important to have this kind of transparency
并让用户知道他们看到的文本是由AI生成的
and let the user know that the text they're seeing was generated by AI
然后我们就输入客户的评论和评论的情绪
Then we'll just input the customer review and the review sentiment
还要注意，这部分不一定很重要
Also note that this part isn't necessarily important
因为我们实际上也可以使用这个提示来提取评论的情绪
because we could actually use this prompt to also extract the review sentiment
然后在后续步骤中，编写电子邮件
and then in a follow-up step, write the email
但是，只是为了这个例子的目的
But just for the sake of the example
好吧，我们已经从评论中提取了情感
well, we've already extracted the sentiment from the review
所以在这里我们有一个给客户的回复
So here we have a response to the customer
它涉及客户在评论中提到的细节
It addresses details that the customer mentioned in their review
并且按照我们的指示
and as we instructed
建议他们与客户服务部联系
suggest that they reach out to customer service
因为这只是一个AI客户服务代理
because this is just an AI customer service agent
接下来，我们将使用语言模型的一个参数，叫做temperature
Next, we're going to use a parameter of the language model called temperature
这将使我们能够改变模型响应的多样性
that will allow us to change the variety of the model's responses
所以你可以把temperature看成
So you can think of temperature as
模型的探索或随机性的程度
the degree of exploration or randomness of the model
因此，对于这个特定的短语
So for this particular phrase
我最喜欢的食物是
my favorite food is
模型预测的最有可能的下一个词是披萨
the most likely next word that the model predicts is pizza
而接下来的两个最可能的
and the next two most likely
它建议是寿司和玉米饼
it suggests are sushi and tacos
因此，在temperature为零的情况下
So at a temperature of zero
模型总是会选择最可能的下一个词
the model will always choose the most likely next word
在这个例子中是比萨
which in this case is pizza
而在更高的temperature下
and at a higher temperature
它也会选择一个不太可能的词
it will also choose one of the less likely words
甚至在更高的temperature下
and at an even higher temperature
它有可能选择玉米饼
it might even choose tacos
虽然这只有5%的机率被选中
which only has a five percent chance of being chosen
你可以想象，当模型继续这个最后的响应
You can imagine that as the model continues this final response
所以我最喜欢的食物是比萨饼
so my favorite food is pizza
而且它继续产生更多的词
and it continues to generate more words
这个响应会与第一个响应发生分歧
this response will diverge from the first response
也就是我最喜欢的食物是玉米饼
which is my favorite food is tacos
所以随着模型的继续
So as the model continues
这两个响应将变得越来越不同
these two responses will become more and more different
一般来说，在构建你想要的应用程序时
In general, when building applications where you want
一个可预测的响应
a predictable response
我建议使用temperature=0
I would recommend using temperature zero
在所有这些视频中
Throughout all of these videos
我们一直在使用temperature=0
we've been using temperature zero
我认为，如果你试图建立一个系统
and I think that if you're trying to build a system that
可靠和可预测的系统，你应该使用这个
is reliable and predictable, you should go with this
如果你想以更有创意的方式使用这个模型
If you're trying to use the model in a more creative way
你可能希望有更多不同的输出
where you might want a wider variety of different outputs
你可能想用更高的temperature
you might want to use a higher temperature
那么，现在让我们把刚才的提示也拿出来
So now let's take this same prompt that we just used
让我们试着生成一封电子邮件
and let's try generating an e-mail
但让我们使用一个更高的temperature
but let's use a higher temperature
所以在我们的get_completion函数中，我们在整个视频中一直在使用
So in our get_completion function that we've been using throughout the videos
我们已经指定了一个模型和一个temperature
we have specified a model and then also a temperature
但我们已经把它们设置为默认值
but we've set them to default
所以现在让我们试着改变temperature
So now let's try varying the temperature
所以我们使用提示
So we use the prompt
然后让我们试试temperature=0.7
and then let's try temperature=0.7
于是用temperature=0
And so with temperature=0
每次你执行同样的提示时
every time you execute the same prompt
你应该期待同样的完成
you should expect the same completion
而在temperature为0.7时
whereas with temperature 0.7
你每次都会得到一个不同的输出
you'll get a different output every time
所以这里我们有我们的电子邮件
So here we have our e-mail
正如你所看到的，它与我们之前收到的电子邮件
and as you can see, it's different to the e-mail
不同
that we received previously
让我们再执行一次，以显示我们将再次得到一个不同的电子邮件
And let's just execute it again to show that we'll get a different e-mail again
这里我们有另一封不同的电子邮件
And here we have another different e-mail
所以我建议你自己玩一下temperature
So I recommend that you play around with temperature yourself
也许你现在可以暂停视频，并尝试这个提示
Maybe you could pause the video now and try this prompt
用各种不同的temperature
with a variety of different temperatures
只是为了看看输出是如何变化的
just to see how the outputs vary
因此，总结一下，在较高的temperature下
So to summarize, at higher temperatures
模型的输出更加随机
the outputs from the model are kind of more random
你几乎可以认为，在较高temperature下
You can almost think of it as that at higher temperatures
助理更容易分心
the assistant is more distractible
但也许更有创造力
but maybe more creative
在下一个视频中，我们将进一步讨论
In the next video, we're going to talk more about
对话补全终端格式
the chat completions endpoint format
以及你如何使用这种格式创建一个自定义的聊天机器人
and how you can create a custom chatbot using this format